That friends, is your purse life insurance
and if not then watch a video, there is
an offer going on at SSC bank, you will
get the police number instantly, it is a number of 2 lakh winters
and you will get it online in a
very short time but you can open it with it
without any document, that is, medical
stores take a mix, but to open the account,
it will have an impact on the shops, will it make
some difference, you just need your mobile,
you can do it, okay friends, you will have to have a savings account of SSC, if you do not have a savings account then zero balance setting on, opening is happening right now, you get equal and see this, you can open a savings account through it, okay friends, I
request you all,
please share the video
and do not forget to like it, so
friends, let's start the video, click ok, that is,
typing savings account, but
today you have to log in to the mobile app,
later you have to click on the status icon,
after clicking ok, then you have to
click on inches, a
You see, you have to click on the app lock,
after clicking you can see,
first you can see my police number,
I had opened online, okay, I
liked it very much, till then I opened it, then I did
not tell people, now I will be able to show people
that you people should take it from Samsung class where
I study, if I go to study then the video will become very bad,
okay then apply the Samsung hunger strike,
after typing and
for this, okay you also have to click on the remaining nine from
above, if I
click on the previous one, then
after clicking it will
take some loading,
see people are taking it,
after that you have to
click on the straight line, then you had
pressed it earlier, that is why it is showing like this,
okay, so let me click on State Gun,
then it is
loading again, that is okay, we will
shoot a little
and there is a problem with the net, that is why it is getting delayed, so
all this has come out,
last over 50 lakhs of these, 50 lakhs now how much or
for this you are taking police, keep decisions against these, you will have to
click everything, okay, be in the
gutkha  If you smoke cigarettes then click on this to
stop smoking if you don't smoke then you will have to click on your loved ones
now people can click on Samay Dharma S Way All No,
your premium will be 722 rupees by clicking on Mandali's Amla,
we will give you 10 rupees in 10 back,
so
after clicking everything you have to click on next,
after clicking if you are married then you will have to click on
real and if you are single then you will have to click on single, so
let me select single
and if you are asking for salary then you will have to do salary slip,
I was thinking that it is
not like that only celebrities can take it or
we can take others also and you have to give these compressors
12 laxmans,
so let me show you a boy also,
what problem comes,
I will have to give the name of the nominee and that is
in the past days, it will automatically come here,
click it,
keep it in a automatically, so let me be the longest, you
people click everything as per your wish, ok
and I will
select anything in the past and you have to
give below how much is the hand of now, that much will be
sitting, both of these have to be clicked,
see this  How many feet is your pure
Pragya Chetak, you will have to give it,
I am fit and 3 inches,
so I can select anything, then do
not make any changes in its size,
if you do
not have to select anything, otherwise you will have to
give how much it is,
I will give you their vision,
just to show you people, I
already have it, I will show you people
how to do the process, so I have put in the system,
all this will be visible once,
after filling up, then next will be clicked,
ok, so how do I see, Akbar
Tughlaq of New Delhi, maximum
annual income has to be given, so I put two lakhs, the
fifth was stopped at 2 lakhs, so it is done, I have
checked everything once, then I have
clicked next, the
next step will come out, do
not leave all this empty, leave all this like this, if
you want to know the full details, then
keep it half filled and
keep the mobile in your hand, lighting and its
team will give you the full information tomorrow, if you
want to join then do it,
I will fill it  If I make a video in details then the
video will become at least 1 hour long, that's why I have
shortened it a bit, if it is a retail slogan then
please contact customer care, ok
your - whatever love is there in front of it, now
it is under its control, so let me cut it, to do the
push later the next step will come out,
see here, it will be debited from the account number, to
debit from the account number you will have to enter
money on a number, ok
then OTP will come on the mobile number, you have to give the OTP,
I will ask you beforehand, I had done it sometime, then
click on the feet, if
I have just seen it, please vote on your account, if I feel like it, it will be
deleted,
now you will get the police number within an hour,
ok, so I had to show this to you people,
but how to open it with this,
ok friends, ok Jai Hind, Jai Bharat, Vande
Maa